

3576 Scofield Avenue, Simi Valley, CA 93063 805-433-5157, dh001@ucr.edu

#### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I'm currently a student attending the University of California Riverside, and am studying computer science. I've previously attend Moorpark College for four years and have earned Associate Degrees for Physics and Mathematics. During my time at school I have also taken many course in computers covering; software construction, algorithms, data structures, object oriented programming, c++, java, and python. I'm also a member of the Moorpark computer science club and spend free time researching new programming techniques and tools.

## **SKILLS**

- C++ (OOP, algorithms/data structures)
- Java

Python

- Algebra, calculus (entire series with analytical Geometry), differential equations, and
- MatLab

• Introduction to linear algebra

- Unit Testing (\*using google "gtest" framework)
- Physics (electromagnetism, waves, and optics, thermodynamics, Newtonian mechanics,)

#### **EXPERIENCE**

Delivery Driver | Domino's Pizza | Simi Valley, CA

February 2016 - Current

 Delivering food to customers Taking orders and handling money Customer Service.

Delivery Driver | East Coast Pizza Company | Simi Valley, CA

July 2014 - February 2016

Delivering food to customers Taking orders and handling money
Customer Service Taking Inventory.

#### **EDUCATION**

Associate of Science January 2018

Moorpark College, Moorpark, CA

Associate of Science January 2018

Moorpark College, Moorpark, CA

Associate of Science January 2018

Moorpark College, Moorpark, CA

## **INTERESTS**

Activities and Honors,

Member of the Moorpark Computer Science Club (2015-2018)

Member of the Moorpark Math Club (2016-2018)

Member of the Moorpark Space Club (2017-2018)

Github username: dhuecker

# **ADDITIONAL INFORMATION**

- Dean's List (2014-2015) G.P.A (3.32)
- Founder of RetroPiGaming -> www.RetroPiGaming.com (January 2019)